Aníbal VR







Full Stack Web Developer

SUMMARY

A self-motivated, fast leaner and hard working person, I love web development and learning new technologies. My focus is bringing an awesome user experience into all my projects. Experienced with marketing, web and android development.

SKILLS

Front-End Technologies

- React
- React Hooks
- o Redux
- Responsive CSS3
- Sass
- o JQuery
- o Bootstrap
- Material UI

Back-end Technologies

- NodeJS
- ExpressJS
- o MongoDB
- Mongoose
- o MVC Pattern

EXPERIENCE

Freelance – Full Stack Developer

2018 - Present

- Creating high quality apps and websites.
- o Writing clean, readable and modular code using best practices and programming patterns
- o Managing content, SEO and Digital Marketing for clients (Google Ads)

West World Games – Freelance Game Developer | Publisher

2017-2018

- o Developed and design apps for Android
- Published application in the PlayStore
- Design images and UI/UX
- Developed Google Ads campaigns.
- Worked with C# and Unity

Visit: https://avr00.github.io/my_portfolio/

PERSONAL PROJECTS

<u>Headnews</u> – React / Redux / Redux Thunk / Axios / Newsapi

React application that renders the most important news from different countries and languages.

Visit Project: https://jolly-hypatia-445f35.netlify.com/us/general

My Notes - React / Axios / Material-UI / MongoDB / NodeJS / ExpressJS / Heroku

Application to take notes it was made using the MVC pattern and the MERN Stack.

Visit Project: https://my-notes-mern.herokuapp.com/

React Password Generator – React / Sass

React application that allows you to create strong password for best security with a beautiful UI

Visit Project: https://festive-nightingale-d10ab1.netlify.com/

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration Specialized in Marketing

Technological University of Chile INACAP (2013-2018)

Front-End Libraries Certificate

freeCodeCamp (2017)

Responsive Web Design Certificate

freeCodeCamp (2017)